The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
A brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
A way from the moon's sky.
Wearing in the troubled waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for.
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began,
over seas of green and shores of sand,
through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me,
someday somewhere I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere.
Own stupid fault she'd
be okay if she hadn't
helped us and I'm not
sure she can trust that.
Sky knight he pretty
much gives me the creeps
he's kind of old and weird but he doesn't
seem like that bad of a guy there was no
other choice I want to protect her but it's
not like we could have
brought her along with
us man this piece of
junk is slow of course
it is it's got to be several times heavier
than a standard waiver what'd you expect.
Guys where did that
huge forest come from is
that the upper yard I don't
remember this being on
the map wait no there is
supposed to be a forest
ahead but I don't see
any warning about how big
it is this cannot be
right who knows how old
that map is we know it can
be traced back a couple
hundred years but who's
to say it hasn't been
around longer the forest
may have been a fraction of.
of its size when that map was made.
Ah, that's true.
All I know is I gotta
climb one of those trees.
They're enormous.
Look, the entrance.
Well, this is it, Usopp.
If you're gonna chicken
out, now's the time.
Actually, if you don't mind, I was
kind of thinking I'd like to go back.
Too late!
Then why didn't you ask me?
What was that?
Would you calm down?
Yeah, take it easy.
Open your eyes!
Don't you notice anything strange?
Look at all these shipwrecks!
It is a forest.
He's right.
That doesn't make any sense!
Besides, they didn't run aground,
they were sliced in half!
Did you hear that?
The woods are full of noises! Relax!
I heard that.
Full speed ahead!
Oh, a handful!
Stroke!
What's going on?
A sickle monster! Hang on tight!
Here comes another one!
No, not just one.
Paddle like crazy!
What the hell is this?
That's where you're going!
Faster, Luffy!
No, wait, slow down!
This isn't working!
Usak, take the wheel! Gum-Gum!
What are you doing?
It's in front of us!
I know, just hang on!
That man dodged it!
Whoa, that was close!
I think we finally outran it.
Oh, but this is bad.
Now it's too late to go back.
I can't even see the entrance anymore.
Then stay here.
I'd die, you idiot!
More than likely.
Was that a big snake?
Looked like a giant lamprey.
Sky lamprey, I guess.
One that big will do more
than just suck a little blood.
Neatest forest ever, huh?
Neat forest my butt!
If this is our so-called
ordeal, then I quit!
You can't quit yet, we just got here!
We've got to keep moving.
We can't spend any more time on
this milky road than necessary.
Otherwise, we're asking for certain death.
There he is! Zoro!
It's all my fault!
What if he gets swallowed?
Why hasn't he come back up?
Zoro, please be okay!
You don't think he got eaten, do you?
Zoro's fish food!
If he had been eaten, the clouds
would have turned red by now.
How can you stay so calm
at a time like this?
I am so done with you!
I can tell you one thing, we are not
going to make it across by swimming.
What kind of swordsman punches a
shark instead of using his blade?
I'm so glad you're okay!
One thing's for certain, we're definitely
somewhere in the middle of Upper Yard.
Hmm, this seems to be some sort of
altar for sacrifices. Hey, look!
There's a giant head blocking our way!
Not quite. It's a statue. Oh, right.
But it looks like a total dead end.
No, look, there's four entrances.
Of course.
And how much you want to bet all four
of them lead to different places.
You think we get to take our pick?
Is it me, or do none of these things
really sound like much of an ordeal?
I don't know, guys.
Which one should we choose?
Prepare for judgment, criminals.
You have no choice but to receive it.
Select a gate.
Select from four ordeals.
For you, there can be no turning back.
You may choose your own trial,
but we will decide your fate.
Swamp
Isle
Strain
Spheres
Choose your path, criminals?
So what do we do?
Um, let's go with spheres
Why do you like that one?
Spheres are like balls, right?
Sounds fun That's your only reason?
They're ordeals, they're not supposed to
be fun Not that I'm disagreeing with you.
Spheres is definitely the one that
doesn't sound too violent at least to me.
That's decided!
Just don't let your guard down, guys.
Remember, these are God's islands,
ten thousand meters above sea level.
Anything can happen. Ready!
Let's do this!
Driver, would you mind
not shutting your eyes?
No, it's just as dark with them open.
Hey guys, what if this is
like one of those games?
Like a what?
You know, if you pick the right
door, then you get a prize.
But if you pick the wrong one...
What are you talking about?
What if we picked wrong?
Why couldn't you have
mentioned this before, Luffy?
Well, let's see here.
Um, if you pick the wrong one,
then you fall off the island.
How can you say something so stupid?
We're thousands of meters in the air!
I don't know how many times your life can
flash before your eyes
during a fall like that,
and I don't want to know!
You guys are both being idiots.
Nothing like that's gonna...
You've got to be kidding me!
Ah!
There's an entire school of them!
What are we going to do?
I'm not sure,
but if that first one was any indication,
we're not going to have
much luck fighting them off.
We've got to do something.
We can't stay here forever.
Leaving us here was that
lobster's idea of a joke?
It's not very funny.
Perhaps this is the heaven's judgment
we've been hearing so much about.
Except you'd think this god would try
something a little flasher, you know?
Eh, couldn't say.
Never met the guy.
I'm not sure what the solution is.
We definitely can't set sail
with the hull looking like this.
Hey, Chopper, try to figure out
a way to fix the ship. Me? Okay.
Why should he fix it?
Are you going somewhere?
I'm gonna find a way into the forest.
We should probably make
this our base of operations.
You guys can keep a lookout.
I'm sure Luffy and the
others are headed this way.
Like they say, if you get lost, you
should stay where you are, right?
Shouldn't that apply to you two?
Zoro, if you want to go into the forest,
well, I guess that's okay with me.
But you haven't really told us what for.
There's supposed to be some
kind of god on this island.
I want to meet him. Wait!
That's a terrible idea.
I mean, what are you going to
do when you actually find him?
I don't know.
Depends on if he behaves himself.
Zoro, you're the bravest person I know.
And what about his priests?
You going to beat them up too?
Hello?
The last thing we need
is you pissing off a god.
It's kind of not smart.
By the time I'm done with him,
this god's going to bow before me.
I don't believe in him anyway.
What do I care about pissing him off?
Oh, powerful one.
I just want you to know I don't
agree with my idiot shipmate.
I don't even like him that much.
Okay, bye.
That vine looks pretty sturdy.
Ah, excellent idea.
Mind if I tag along, swordsman?
Sure, as long as you promise not
to slow me down. Wait a minute!
Where do you think you're going?
Look at this.
At least a thousand years have
passed since this altar was built.
A thousand years?
The sense of history here is amazing.
It gives me chills.
You feel it?
A place as ancient as this is sure to
be filled with all kinds of old relics.
Imagine all the valuables
we could discover.
Just think, the possibilities are endless.
In that case, I'll join you.
Nami, I thought you were too scared.
It's for history.
Yeah, sure it is.
It's official.
He's lost his mind.
She made it!
Looks easy enough.
This is higher up than
I thought. Be careful.
If you fall, you'll most certainly die.
That's supposed to be
your idea of helping?
Whoa, she's right.
I'm dead if I fall.
Mommy?
Help me!
It's too fast! I'm in a crash!
Look at that.
You're not gutless.
Thanks for catching me.
Anytime.
That's what you should have done.
That had nothing to do with it!
This forest is even bigger than I thought.
Okay, Chopper, you're
in charge of the ship!
We're counting on you.
We'll be back soon!
Bye, everyone be careful.
Don't take too long, okay?
I guess nami will be alright
since she's with robin and zoro.
My friends are all so
brave and adventurous!
I'm too scared to go, but maybe someday?
If I'm really lucky, I can
be brave like them, too.
Oh, well, if I can't be brave, I
can at least make myself useful.
Being left alone in the
middle of a dangerous forest
to fix our ship is proof
that everyone must trust me,
so I have to do my very best.
It's just little old me all by
myself in the big, scary forest.
Oh, no!
Who's gonna protect me?
We're alive?
I seriously thought we were falling
all the way back to the blue sea.
That's because somebody had to
make up a lane story to scare us!
I was scared!
I thought I was a goner too!
Alright, so what is this place?
A forest. With balls.
they're balls made of island
cloud awesome they look like
really big snowflakes now what
could be scary about that?
see you stop it's okay heads up the milky
road is leading us up into the trees
i just don't see how this is an ordeal
do you not yet it'd be great if there was
nothing ahead but somehow i doubt it what
if it was like one of those games and we
picked the right door and now all we have
to do is float around in this giant snow
looking for the others
yeah maybe that's it
you're still being idiots they think we're
criminals i doubt they'll let us off that
easy use your brains for once i wouldn't
be surprised if there were more traps like
the ones earlier we have to stay sharp
let's just keep moving what are you the
captain now can we at least have a snack?
oh yeah what you got in the bag?
sanji come on give me?
no no snacks but sanji we need to keep our
strength just a little something i said no
now listen it's really simple i'm going to
keep steering you guys
keep watch out the sides
whoa i didn't realize how high up we were
getting something's not
right it's too quiet there
are four priests so i
assume each tunnel would
lead to one why haven't
we seen any of them yet?
i got a bad feeling about
this okay okay i got it
i got it gosh i thought
i told you to keep watch
Okay, didn't see that coming.
Ah!
Such a cloud ball! Kick it away!
I do not like the idea of
being surrounded by snake eggs.
This can't be good.
For crying out loud!
What's with these things?
Silly children These are surprise clouds!
You never know what's
going to come out of them!
Pete, where's that voice coming from?
I'm so glad you picked my
challenge, the Ordeal of Spears!
Yeah, is that a talking dumpling?
This guy is one of Inaru's priests?
That's the ordeal, ball guy?
Stop with the dancing
and tell us who you are!
Gotta say, he's not as
bright as I expected.
Didn't Nami and the old guy
say these priests were strong?
Because I'm not seeing it.
Hey, Dumpling!
Nami and the others better be safe!
The sacrifices?
They'll escape or they won't.
Doesn't really matter which.
If they escape, they'll die.
If they're sacrificed,
well, they'll die then too.
What's that mean?
But I'd be more worried about yourselves.
You'll have to beat me if you
plan on going any further.
And I really don't see that happening.
He's coming right for us, Luffy. Get him!
I hope you're ready for this.
Come, come!
Oh, you're gonna stretch?
Pistol!
No way! Luffy!
Luffy you're okay aren't you a hit
like that couldn't have hurt you
that much well you see It's not what
you call a normal hit I'll show you
not normal right foot high kick
Only the most well trained will grant
the power of mantra impossible how
could he You've predicted my attack.
No, Sanji!
I warned you, didn't I?
Impact!
The shock destroys the
body from the inside out.
Sanji, Usopp.
Yeah, I'm fine.
What did that bastard do to us?
I got no idea.
Who is this guy anyway?
My name is Scar.
I am one of the four priests
of the almighty Eneru!
Who watch over Upper Yard?
and see to the judgment of
criminals like yourselves.
I own the birth in this lost forest.
The lost forest? Why, yes.
My forest in all its glory.
And now, your boat will
be lost in its illusions.
We're using that!
She will now speed along the Milky Road,
eventually weaving her way
to this forest's only exit.
I'm sure I don't need to tell you this,
but if you lose a dial boat in here,
it's the same as losing your
way to the sacrificial altar
that means you will have to find the boat
and board her before
that happens of course,
my hundreds of surprise clouds and
i will never allow you that chance
Does that seem unfair to you boys?
Welcome to the upper yard.
The ordeal of spheres.
There's a 10 % survival rate.
So good luck.
Survival rate?
Just 10 %?
10 %?